

Mehmet Alp ER Suluova, 16.08.1992 mehmetalper120 gmail.com +49 178 3755889

Address Bahnhofstraße 11B 85774 Unterföhring Germany

MEHMET ALP ER

Electrical and Electronics Engineer

About Me Electrical and Electronics Engineer with more than two years of experience in aerospace, automotive and software development industries. Currently third semester M.Sc. student at Technical University of Munich in Biomedical Engineering and Medical Physics. Focused on machine learning and deep learning applications on images.

Education

2021/09 - 2023/09, Technical University of Munich

M.Sc. Biomedical Engineering and Medical Physics Munich, GERMANY

2011/09 - 2018/12, Middle East Technical University

B.Sc. Electrical and Electronics Engineering Ankara, TURKEY

Experience

Sep 2019 - Oct 2021, *Electrical Design Engineer*, MAN TRUCK AND BUS

Detailed achievements:

- Worked on new electrical systems for the new bus models using:
 - AUCOTEC's Engineering Base Cable (EBCL)
 - Siemens' LDorado Suite
- Took part in:

Selection of components

System design

Electrical wiring diagram

Confirmation of designed systems by others

Feb 2018 - Jun 2019, *Project Staff*, TURKISH AEROSPACE INDUSTRIES

Detailed achievements:

- Worked on a project to build an aircraft in the VLA(Very-Light Aircraft) category with students from various faculties
- Took part in:

Avionic instrument selection and avionic system design Electrical system design

Software Development Skills

Programming

PythonCC#

Computer Software Tools

- AUCOTEC EBCL
 Git
 LDorado
- JIRA

Mehmet Alp ER Suluova, 16.08.1992 mehmetalper12@ gmail.com +49 178 3755889

Address Bahnhofstraße 11B 85774 Unterföhring

Germany

Languages

English
German
Turkish

Courses Taken

Biomedical Physics I-II

Image Processing in Physics

Computer Aided Medical Procedures I-II

Application of Radioactivity in Industry, Research and Medicine

Chemistry in Biomedical Imaging for Physicists

Introduction to Deep Learning

Laboratory Course: Micro Computed Tomography